Come... It will all be alright.
It will be alright. Come...
Kanyumaz!
Find a carriage!
We will carry the injured
people to the tribe! Come on!
You'll be alright!
Alaeddin!
Brother... Brother...
You'll be alright!
Brother!
What do you think you are doing, huh?
Why did you retreat in the middle of the battle?
Why did you leave us alone
in the hands of infidels?!
This is battle!
Retreating is as normal as fighting!
I retreated to protect
the lives of our valiants!
You will answer for...
...all the things you did...
..before my father!
Enough!
I had enough!
Why do you think you are right every time?!
Alaeddin!
You..
...by retreating...
...made the biggest mistake in your life!
You fled from that battlefield in fear.
You are...
You are a coward, Alaeddin!
I am at least...
...a coward who worries
about the lives of our men!
But you are...
...an unaware man who drags his men to death!
You are nothing else!
You shouldn't have done this Orhan Bey!
You shouldn't have done this!
-Done what, huh?
Who are you? Who are you to hit me?!
How could you leave your brother alone there?
Who are you to hit me?!
How could you betray your Alps and martyrs?!
Who are you to hit me?! Let me!
2 DAYS AGO
Attention!
Osman Bey!
Peace be upon you.
Peace be upon you too.
Thanks to..
...Allah Who let us gather...
..in this tent.
Thanks to Him.
You may sit.
With..
...Almighty Allah's 99 names
Who says "Be" and it is...
...and fills our heart with faith...
...let's start the council.
In the name of Allah,
the merciful, the compassionate.
With my Allah's permission and
blessings, we made our state free.
Now our first duty is to...
..help the people oppressed
by the Mongol tyranny.
It is my decision, Alaeddin Bey.
My Bey.
Whoever suffered under this oppression...
...we will take them under
the wings of our state.
As my Bey orders.
You know your duty Orhan Bey.
We will restore our army to
its former strength and might.
This duty is yours.
Sure, my Bey.
In our eternal duty, we will surely
continue to shed blood and sweat...
...without hesitation on the path of...
...martyrdom and war.
Thank Allah.
Our target is clear.
The destination that lies in our hearts is...
...the position that stands
as a barrier before Bursa
and has been seized and
fortified by Byzantium, Derince.
As we always advance toward our goal...
...the infidels make their moves as well.
Right Orhan?
True, my Bey.
The intelligence we received is that...
...an infidel commander
named Gladius, along with
his army, is coming to
Bursa to support them.
Even if they gather everyone before Bursa...
...no one can make us give up on this path.
The Alps have been watching
the outpost for some time.
Soon, we will descend upon those infidels...
...like a dark cloud.
Near Forward Byzantine Headquarters
They are doing something at the outpost.
They might set out for an ambush.
Go and inform Osman Bey now! Go!
Yes my Bey!
Who are you?
Alps!
Attack!
Who are you?
I am the last man...
..you will see in your life.
My Bey.
Koca Bey, who is one of
the Turkmen Beys settled
near Aleppo, requests to
be admitted to the council.
Let him in.
As you order, my Bey.
Kanyumaz.
Here my Bey.
Peace be upon you.
Peace be upon you too.
Koca Bey.
Welcome.
So...
...what brought you here from our...
...ancestors' lands Aleppo?
Tell us.
Your ancestors, right...
It was your grandfather Suleyman Shah
who first chose me as an Alp, Osman Bey.
May he be accepted in heaven.
Aameen, aameen.
He showed great effort on me.
Well..
...I was an Alp..
...and I became a Bey.
This was our fate...
We separated our ways with Kayi...
...and we were away from each other.
Now we are here to tell you to...
...unite our paths and cause.
Okay.
Tell me.
Why should we unite the paths...
...that were separated once?
Huh, Koca Bey?
We thought Aleppo would be our homeland.
When you came to the frontiers, we stayed there.
But..
...when I hear about your victories...
...a storm breaks in here.
I tell myself "O, great old Koca Bey...
Before the light of your eyes goes out...
...go to Dark Osman...
...and kill infidels on frontiers!"
Hay Praise be.
Koca Bey...
My grandfather Suleyman Shah...
...made you an Alp for a reason.
One of my companions who are around Tabriz...
...the leader of valiants, Hasan
Bey wants the same thing.
He wanted me to let you know that.
Alright, alright.
So...
...we have room for everyone...
...whose heart burns with
the fire of war in our tribe.
Your way is my way now.
May Allah keep you with us, Osman Bey.
Thank you, thank you.
Welcome Koca Bey.
Welcome.
Attention!
Osman Bey!
Long live Osman Bey!
O people!
My Beys!
My sisters!
My Alps!
Our council is over.
We strengthened our unity!
As we share our problems and sufferings...
...we will share our meals now.
Come on.
Look me in the eye!
It is time to meet you now, Osman.
We’re bound with our souls
To this land, to these hands
Line up like a mountain
Let’s unite, hand in hand, come
We’re bound with our souls
To this land, to these hands
Line up like a mountain
Let’s unite, hand in hand, come
Come, my sister, come, my brother
Let’s stand as one, let’s be a fist together
Let no more hearts burn in sorrow
Let not this land be torn apart
Come, my sister, come, my brother
Let’s stand as one, let’s be a fist together
Let no more hearts burn in sorrow
Let not this land be torn apart
Live on, live on, live on my people!
Even if we die, we will not bow to strangers
Even in hardship, in struggle,
I would give my life
For the strength of my heroic people
Even if we die, we will not bow to strangers
Even in hardship, in struggle,
I would give my life
For the strength of my heroic people
The Turk's arm will never be broken
The Turk's power will never be drained
Once a flag is raised
It will never fall again
The Turk's arm will never be broken
The Turk's power will never be drained
Once a flag is raised
It will never fall again
Live on, live on, live on my people!
Praise be!
What a nice voice, Boran!
Thank you, my Bey.
Live long, live long.
My Bey.
A villager named Nicos from your
people has something to tell you.
My Bey.
Come here.
Don't hesitate.
Sit at our table, share our meal.
My Bey.
Thank you.
Thanks to you, our tables are
overflowing with abundance, my Bey.
I am here to..
Forgive me, my Bey.
What happened, tell me.
Your Alps, my Bey.
What is the thing that you
want to say but you can't?
While we were plowing near the Derince area...
...we witnessed that the Byzantine soldiers...
...attacked your Alps, my Bey.
My Bey, those are the Alps who have
been watching the Byzantine outpost.
Beys.
Come with me
Take Nicos too.
He will come with us.
Welcome, my Bey.
Welcome Osman Bey. Welcome, my Bey.
My Bey, welcome. Welcome.
Is there another witness?
Yes, my Bey. My wife, Elefterya.
She saw it and told me, my Bey.
What did you see?
I was breastfeeding my baby
when I saw it, I told Nicos.
So, how many were they?
My Bey, there were about fifty.
What is happening, Boran Bey?
My Bey is trying to understand if
we were lured into a trap, Koca Bey.
Be patient.
It's quite old.
It's old, my Bey.
How long have you been using it?
It was my father's, my Bey.
May God forgive his sins.
Good.
Come to the tribe...
...and renew your plow.
Thank you, my Bey.
Let's go take our martyrs.
But we must be careful.
The ambushers may still be there.
Osman took the bait. I
wish we had killed them here.
Wait..
This is just the beginning.
This place will turn into a bloodbath.
Osman will gather his Alps
for revenge and raid the outpost.
What am I going to do?
I will prepare a beautiful welcome for him.
I need to go to Bursa for preparations.
I'm also eager to see that devil.
Your greed is almost frightening me.
What's this anger, Poena?
It's not Poena.
Halime.
What the hell are you talking about?
Poena.
Something happened.
Tell me.
What are you hiding from me?
I am not hiding anything.
I am just...
..eager for revenge.
Aunt...
My Allah, what kind of treachery is this?
I've never seen such
treacherous thing in my life.
We bury our grudges in the
ground along with our enemies.
But these devils have no respect
or mercy, even for the dead.
Indeed we belong to Allah,
and indeed to Him we will return.
Never say that those martyred
in the cause of Allah are dead.
In fact, they are alive!
But you do not perceive it.
I will make those who did this...
...learn the word of Allah in such a way that..
...for every drop of blood shed by my martyrs...
...I will make their blood flow like rivers.
Let's go, let's raid their outposts, my Bey.
No, we can't move without precautions.
First, we'll take precautions.
My Bey! My Bey!
My Bey, we received important information
from the woodcutters in the forest.
My Bey, the infidels who left the outpost have
set a trap for the Turkmen unit on the road.
Go to the tribe, take our martyrs.
As you order, my Bey.
-As you order, my Bey.
We are leaving.
Sofia.
What are you doing here?
How can you ask me that?
Besides missing you?
I said... what are you doing here?
Damn it.
Did the emperor send you for support?
How could the emperor
find someone better than me?
And I thought to myself
What could give me more
pleasure than taking Osman's head?
I thought it was seeing you.
I volunteered for the mission.
To protect...
..you and this beautiful Bursa.
You dastards!
You treacherous infidels!
Dastard dogs!
Come on valiants!
Attack!
Allah is the Greatest!
Koca Bey...
Kill the infidels!
You infidels! Did you eat
barley instead of bread?
The leader of valiants my brother Hasan!
You found this old man again, huh?
Of course, I found him.
There was a big mountain we leaned on.
I thought I should go and find it.
You say the mountains came together, huh?
Come here, my brother.
Thanks to the One Who let us come together!
The ruler Osman Bey!
So, the one who saved our lives
was the ruler of frontiers Osman Bey.
Thank you.
Would Oghuz ever wait something
in return for another Oghuz' help?
Koca Bey spoke of you and your intentions.
We still want the same thing. We
want to pledge our allegiance and unite.
But before that, I have
some important information.
Tell me.
The deaths of Esenbike and
Sargun threw Olcaytu into hot flames.
Those fires burned all
the Turkmen around Tabriz.
Now..
...the leader of the Mongol Noyans, Olcaytu's
most bloodthirsty sword, Orluk Kucar.
He is coming to the frontiers as an envoy.
He will take the bodies of Esenbike and Sargun.
Is Orluk Kucar..
...coming as an envoy?
My Bey, the Mongols have never sent someone
as an envoy in this position before.
So, there is a bigger
danger than the one we have.
Alaeddin, Cerkutay.
Go and welcome the envoy immediately.
They need to be cautious as
they come to these borders.
-As you order my Bey.
Aykurt.
Thank you.
The information you brought
is very important to us.
Welcome to the borders.
Thank you, Osman Bey.
Sofia.
I will never trust you, Glaudius.
I've told you before.
You...
You betrayed my father.
Your father was a very greedy man.
Very greedy.
Shut up!
And I am a man loyal to the emperor.
Just like you.
That's why you're still alive.
That's why you're still here.
I'm still here too.
Despite everything.
Despite you betraying our love.
I was never in love with you.
Never?
Never.
The hearts you left broken behind...
...don't concern you, of course.
You don't care.
But Osman..
We care about Osman.
Olcaytu's son and daughter couldn't kill Osman.
But if we unite...
...we will kill that shepherd.
What do you know about Osman?
You know that outpost Osman wants to take back?
I killed the men guarding it.
Then I went to the tribe.
I looked into Osman's eyes...
...and told him how his men were killed.
I didn't tell him who did it, of
course, unnecessary information.
I got to know Osman.
I saw how his Alps lived.
I looked into Osman's eyes.
I saw his greed, his anger.
What do you think?
Do you think I know him a little?
I even...
I even know where Osman will attack first.
He will attack the outpost to take revenge...
...but I will be waiting for him there.
Gladius..
Where is your army?
Half of my army is settled near the outpost
Osman wants to take back, waiting for my orders.
What about the other half?
The other half... Yes, it's important.
Because they are my most trusted and loved men.
They are coming to me.
They are coming here.
I promise you, Sofia.
Turks won't find a hole to hide.
They won't.
Hasan Bey will stay with us.
He came from far away.
There are Turkmen tribes around Tabriz.
Welcome.
Thank you.
Here, Hasan Bey.
My Bey...
You don't seem alright.
Something must have happened.
Koca Bey heard.
Olcaytu's envoy will come...
...to take Esenbike and Sargun's bodies.
One trouble goes, another one comes.
What are you thinking
about, my gazelle-eyed one?
It's been days...
There's still no news from Meryem, my Bey.
Don't worry. The Alps are searching everywhere.
They will surely find a trace.
Where would she go without informing
us? What if something happened to her?
No, she is brave. Nothing
will happen to her, don't worry.
She will come back safe and sound, God willing.
May Allah not punish us for this but...
Sometimes I think if we are being
tested with losing our loved ones.
We lost Meryem before we
could come together with Halime.
My Bala, there is good in everything.
Aren't we the biggest witnesses of this?
Huh?
If there were no separation, what
meaning would there be in reunion?
But this reunion is very close.
It is close.
We got over many hardships...
Now we are with our family in our tribe.
I thought you were gone.
I thought the breath I took was killing me.
But then I found you again.
Then we heard the good news...
We found out that our daughter is alive.
The fire that had gone out in
our hearts started burning again.
My Bala, this separation
will soon turn into reunion.
We will reunite with Halime and Meryem.
God willing.
Speaking of Halime...
I have something to tell you, Osman.
Tell me.
You are the horse of the tribe.
Now...
You will take this letter to
the tribe and be my confidant.
Go, my girl.
Go, my girl! Go!
Go!
Ruin Gladius' game!
Stop the horse! Catch it!
Calm down... Calm down...
Ssh..
My girl...
Let's see who you are sending this letter to.
Soldiers!
Priestess Lucia...
...died before she could
tell us where Halime was.
We just know her name and
that she is with Sofia, huh?
Correct.
But we are also looking for her in Bursa.
In Bursa...
You know, Holofira knows people in
Bursa... She knows an easy way to go there.
So I say... I can go there secretly.
With a few people, I will take our daughter
and come back before someone sees us, huh?
No Bala. No.
Sofia is in Bursa.
She knows we are after her.
That's why she controls every step we take.
Besides...
Finding Halime won't be that easy.
We'll take precautions. We'll find a secret way.
You are dreaming!
You are dreaming.
Don't you know Sofia?
Don't you know her games?
Besides, if it were that easy, would I
leave my daughter in their hands, huh?
I might be dreaming Osman...
I am strong enough to chase that dream.
If our daughter is there, I cannot stay here.
Bala.
I will not let this happen.
No.
Sofia is a demon.
She is trying to attack
us by using our daughter.
You might go to Bursa...
But you'll never be able to leave.
I cannot put you at risk.
Don't, my Bala. Don't.
This fire is our fire.
Your heart is in flames.
Do you think mine is not?
Do you think I am stone hearted?
Since the day I found out about the truth...
...I haven't been able to sleep.
My gazelle eyed love.
They turned her against us.
They made her her tribe's enemy.
Think about it...
Those gazelle eyes...
...will look at us like we are her enemies.
She will.
If you are her mother, I am her father.
I am her father.
It hurts too much, Osman.
This hope hurts even more.
It tires us even more.
Let me go.
Please, let this longing end.
I won't let you go there alone.
Don't be upset.
Don't worry.
We will find Halime and Meryem. Don't worry.
We will set out together. We will
fight together. We will find them.
Don't worry.
I told you many lies
I made many mistakes.
I have no courage to look at your faces.
I am embarrassed. I didn't know.
There is a truth that is hard
to believe and say for me.
I am your daughter.
Their daughter?!
The Emperor sent Gladius
with a big army to Sofia for help.
I wanted you to know this.
Aunt..
My daughter...
Don't...
They trust themselves so much
that they don't even guard the place.
They just eat.
They came to the frontiers...
...they have thousands of enemies...
..but..
...they didn't take precautions, huh?
There is something behind this.
-This is strange. -Dastard dogs.
Come on.
Let's get closer to them.
Who are you, you demons?
These are apparently the mute ones.
They were trained with Chinese methods.
Stop!
Step back!
You thought we did not take
measures and attacked us, huh?
Who are you? Why are you here?
-We are Osman Bey's Alps.
You are Osman Bey's Alps, huh?
They thought you were not equal to
them, and they did not draw their swords...
Or else, they would bury you all here.
Taking our lives is not that easy, dear Envoy.
Many like you...
...died by our sword.
You are in the lands of Kayi.
Know your limits!
You should be thankful...
You should be thankful Osman's Alp... Or else...
Or else? Or else what?
-Or else...
I will kill you all here!
No one could stand against
the great Ilkhanid Empire!
Are you the ones to stand against it?
Get ready.
We are going to the Kayi tribe.
We will accompany you.
So you will lead the way for me, huh?
You can only crawl behind me.
Many Mongol envoys like you...
...spoke like you.
If you keep speaking like this...
...you will die like they did.
Know this!
Those men beat us up, my Shahzade.
They also made us drop our swords...
We were caught unaware.
But my Shahzade... I hope his
army is different than those few warriors!
I hope so!
We will not give up, Cerkutay Bey. We won't.
We will go after them.
Come on now. Come on.
You will find every child of
Osman in his family for me.
I will take a girl...
...and a boy from his family as a retaliation...
...to Olcaytu Khan.
If he does not give them,
we'll take them by force.
Come on!
So you decided that you've missed me. Come.
The frontier lands are in a chaos.
Olcaytu sent Mongols' most
bloodthirsty man Kucar...
...to Osman as an envoy.
Osman made a big mistake.
He got himself into a big
trouble by killing those barbarians.
I was the one..
...who got Osman into this trouble.
How?
I killed Esenbike and Sargun...
...and let Olcaytu attack Osman.
You know... This mind of yours that is
overshadowed by your beauty... I admire it.
I wonder..
...if that same mind thought
about what Osman will do...
...to us when he finds out about this?
Are you afraid?
Never..
When I kill Osman tomorrow...
...Bitinia will be all
clean. Every corner of it.
Still..
Get ready to meet Kucar.
After Osman..
...with us, in private.
Yes, with us.
He wants to have dinner together and talk.
-Good.
I'll be there as well.
Someone needs to be there...
...and control your anger.
Attention! Osman Bey!
Osman!
Envoy Kucar, huh?
We've been waiting for you.
Before the Mongols reach their destination,
the wind always comes before their body.
In your raids on your frontiers,
you learned who we were, Osman.
Enemies must know each other well.
The end of your arrival to the frontiers...
...will be the proof of
your departure from here.
The Khan of Khans, Olcaytu Khan who rules
the world is coming to the frontiers...
..not to return this time.
Of course, you can calm his anger.
But for now, you will give
the bodies of Khanzades.
Esenbike and Sargun.
Here are their bodies.
Give the order of our Khan to Osman.
Only your knowing is not enough, Osman.
Your Beys and your people must
also know the fate you have led them to.
Our glorious Khan Olcaytu...
...under one condition.
In return for Esenbike
Hatun and Sargun, Osman...
..will give..
..a son and..
...a daughter from his family...
...to our great Khan Olcaytu.
If he doesn't...
Mongols...
...let alone the people of Kayis...
...let alone its Beys...
...will kill even the birds and
sheep that live on these lands!
Olcaytu's grandson and daughter...
We did not take their lives.
Do you have proof of this?
I have no proof, and Allah is my only witness.
But..
...of course I will...
...prove my word.
Now..
...go and tell your Khan.
Osman Bey...
...never...
...obeys the infidels.
Then spend enough time
with your children, Osman.
Your blood will flow like a
river to the frontier lands soon.
Kayi...
Bursa, and every piece of land
that is close to the frontiers...
...will be ruled by Ilkhanids.
Olcaytu will destroy you.
Come on.
We are leaving.
Tell your Khan, envoy.
...you want to take the lives of my children...
...I will be waiting here to rip your heart out!
Go now!
My Beys!
My Alps!
We have never..
...bowed before infidels, and
we will never bow! We saw...
...death as shahada...
...and grave as our positions!
Now tell me..
Are you with me to make Bursa and beyond...
..Muslim lands?
We are!
Thank you.
Thank you, live long.
It's my order. Tomorrow
We will take the lands
the infidels took from us
and that are an obstacle
between us and Bursa.
For the state, for the religion of Islam...
...to spread the name of Turks in the world...
...for the revenge of our
martyrs and veterans, I swear...
...we will never give up on battle!
Allah is the Greatest!
God..
Show me the right way once again.
I committed sins that can never be forgiven.
Welcome, my little bird.
Why didn't you go to sleep?
I had a nightmare.
It's good that you are here.
There is something important
that I want to talk to you about.
Maybe...
You will get really mad at me... Maybe...
...you will hate me...
But...
I cannot carry this secret anymore.
What do you mean?
Aunt?
I always wanted to have a child.
I could not give birth to a child...
...who would carry the blood of Master Yannis.
My biggest enemy...
...caused such a deep wound in a battle that...
...he stole my future.
I will never have a child.
I was in great pain. Poena.
My dreams were stolen from me. I
couldn't have lived without a child.
And that day...
...the last piece of innocence...
...in me was buried under the ground.
-No.
And I...
...kidnapped the daughter of my
enemy who was the reason of this.
What are you saying?
You..
Even if you carry their
blood, you are my daughter.
I was in hell before you.
I was in a dark cold dungeon, but you...
You were a light in that dungeon.
You were the reason for me to live.
But this..
...does not change what I did to you.
It cannot make you forgive it.
But maybe, if you kill me...
...you can relieve...
..your heart.
Kill me now.
Kill me.
You stole my life from me!
Was it for revenge? Revenge!
For revenge..
You took..
...everything from me.
You took everything from me!
-My feelings are real.
You are lying!
My feelings...
...were real, Poena. -No!
You are my daughter!
You are a liar!
You are lying! You are lying!
I can never forgive you!
I will never..
I will never forgive you!
I will never ever forgive you!
Aunt..
You coughed up blood.
Neither God nor you will never forgive me.
And I...
...dreamt of a long life with you
but God will not let that come true.
He already punished me.
I am dying. Poena.
Doctors said I am so sick that...
...I won't even make it to this summer.
Beys...
...all together...
...we will move from both sides. On one side...
...the Byzantium outpost...
...on this hill that is on our
weakest spot and on the other side...
...Gladius' support unit.
Both duties are quite tough, Osman Bey.
So, what is our plan? -Yes, yes.
We will plan everything. Don't worry.
Now...
Orhan, Alaeddin.
Boran, Cerkutay.
Now you..
...will raid the Byzantium outpost together.
You will attack from both sides.
And you will sneak in from here.
Whoever stands..
...on this spot...
...you will turn that place...
...into their graves. As you order, my Bey.
My Bey...
Sure, it is not easy to raid the outpost.
But defeating the support
unit... It's much more difficult.
Therefore, either my brother or I should
come with you my Bey. Those dogs...
...will bring many men along.
-No.
I made my decision.
Koca Bey...
And Hasan Bey.
We'll go there together.
Beys...
...and you will carry out...
...this duty together.
As you order my Bey.
As you order, my Bey
But don't forget.
There is...
...of course shahada on this
way. We might become veterans.
But..
...those who do not live for freedom..
...die in captivity.
Come on now.
-May our war be blessed.
-Aameen. -Aameen.
We heard that...
...you sent the bodies of Esenbike and Sargun...
...to Olcaytu Khan but
you didn't ask for anything...
...from Osman in return.
What they did...
...is disrespectful to you.
You..
...don't worry about Osman, Hatun.
Osman..
...is living his last days.
He will see the furor of Ilkhanid Empire soon.
No one has ever had
the power to stand against
Olcaytu Khan. Osman
won't be able to do so as well.
But...
...there is something we wonder...
When will your armies come to the frontiers?
We never leave our revenge half-finished.
Every creature that stands in our way...
...and that does not bow to us...
...will die and perish.
Now..
I have..
..an offer for you.
The Khan of Khans...
...my glorious Khan Olcaytu Khan...
...wants to make an alliance with you.
The things you say...
...sound like music to me.
Sure..
Osman's enemies...
...are our friends.
Great Roman Empire...
...will make an alliance with
Olcaytu Khan. Don't worry.
Excellent!
I am glad!
It made me really happy.
We..
...will stand next to you in the war...
...you will wage against Turks, Kucar.
Not next to us, Hatun.
At our service.
Pour some.
What do you mean?
Ilkhanid Empire...
...is not looking for friends.
We just want servants...
...who will bow their heads, tie
their hands and kneel before us!
You will give Bursa to us.
Pour some.
What does that mean?
Our target
...is having all the lands in the West.
If you do not bow...
When my glorious ruler Olcaytu comes...
...he will first destroy Osman...
...then these palaces that you trust so much..
...and the walls here and there.
Holy Roman Empire...
...will never bow to anyone! Know that!
It will. It will.
My glorious ruler is so generous that...
...he will let you practice your religion.
You can also trade. Don't
worry about these two things.
And you can also...
...protect your positions.
You will pay us the tax we determine...
...to the Ilkhanid governor
we will appoint for Bursa.
Do you think we are the same
as those looter tribe Beys?
We..
...crush anyone..
...who stands in our way and does not bow.
I am giving you two days.
Think.
And decide.
Will you choose living?
Or dying?
By killing Esenbike and Sargun...
...you put us into a very
difficult position, Sofia.
Now we are not only facing
Osman but also the Ilkhanid state.
As long as I am alive...
...I will never bow down to anyone! And I...
Never!
Stop!
Don't take another step!
That's Osman!
If you take another step, you
will let Azrael take your life.
Do you think you can
...defeat us alone, Osman?
I will skin you out and make it
a sheath for my sword, Osman.
I will drag your miserable body behind my horse.
Look at us, you dastards!
Wolves are not alone!
Wolves are not fools!
Many have come to turn
the frontiers into my grave..
But they all died. Now,
it's time for you to suffer.
Come on.
-Alps!
-Allah is the greatest!
Allah is Eternal!
I have the left wing.
-I have the left wing, brother.
Come on, alps.
We'll sneak in silently.
Come on Cerkutay Bey.
O Allah!
Draw your swords! Allah is the Greatest!
Allah is the Greatest!
Don't let any of them survive, Alps!
Come on Alps! Come on!
They are weaker now Alps! Attack them!
It is falling my Shahzade!
The outpost is falling!
The victory is ours God willing!
Throw!
Alps! Come back!
Kayis! I brought hell to you!
Walk!
Come on Alps! Allah is the Greatest!
My Shahzade! My Shahzade!
We need to retreat! We are losing too many Alps!
They are all becoming martyrs!
-My Allah, help us!
Alps! We are retreating!
Come on! Or we will all die here!
Come on! We will die here! Come on!
Retreat! Retreat!
-Come on!
-Alaeddin!
No, Alaeddin!
Come on!
Alaeddin! What are you doing?
Come on! Come on Cerkutay Bey!
Come on! -Cerkutay Bey!
-Come on brothers!
Alaeddin! Alaeddin!
What are you doing?!
Alaeddin!
Come on! Come on!
Come at me.
You weak infidel...
You thin, dry stick!
Are you going to fight with the great
plane tree, huh? Come on, make your move!
Make your move and I will rip your heart out!
Die Osman!
Were you going to kill me with this sword, huh?
You dastard dog!
My Bey... That coward is
running away, I'll go after him.
Stop!
Hasan Bey... Don't tire yourself, let him go!
Thank Allah.
Don't, my Osman Bey. Are we
going to let that dastard run away?
No.
Let him go.
Don't you want our victory to be heard, huh?
Let him go now.
Let him tell his owner
everything. Let him tell Gladius...
...how they lost.
-There is a pile of treasure in the cart, my Bey.
-Okay.
Okay. So, the sword that
the infidels draw against us...
...will always be driven into their hearts.
Thanks to Allah.
We did not let them win.
-Thank Allah.
Come on now.
Take these.
We are going to the tribe.
Bring the horses.
-As you order, my Bey.
We cannot resist now. They
are coming at us like dogs!
We need to retreat! -Come!
We will resist, Boran Bey! We will resist!
My Shahzade, they left us alone.
We need to retreat, my Shahzade!
We will resist!
Hang on, Alps! Allah is with us! Hang on!
Yusuf!
My Shahzade, we need to retreat, come on!
-Boran Bey, our martyrs...
...our Alps! We cannot leave
them here! We lost many Alps!
We have many martyrs!
Yusuf.
Yusuf! -My Shahzade! -Yusuf!
My Shahzade, Yusuf was martyred.
My Shahzade, don't worry.
We won't leave our martyrs here.
But not now. We need to retreat, my Shahzade.
-Yusuf. -Come on.
Alaeddin, I will make you regret
this! I will make you regret this!
-We are retreating! Come on! Brother!
-Cowards ran away! The fools are here!
Kill them all!
Come on! Come on!
Run, you dogs! Run!
You will never be able to
take this outpost! Never!
He is still alive. Commander Gladius.
Coward Osman did not come here.
He sent his looter Shahzades, right?
You will lose.
I will become a martyr.
-You will lose.
-I will lose?
You are the one fighting
for your life on the ground.
Not me.
You are a dastard dog.
You are destined to lose.
You are too courageous
for a man who is about to die.
Then while you are
approaching hell step by step..
...take the things you believe. Hold on to them.
Because you will need them.
I bear witness that there is none
worthy of worship except Allah...
...and I bear witness that Muhammad
is His servant and Messenger.
Take this dead body to Osman.
With my best intentions.
Kanyumaz! Find a carrier now!
We will take the injured to the tribe! Hurry!
-As you order, my Shahzade!
My Shahzade! -Come.
You'll be alright. You'll be alright. I am here.
You'll be alright. You'll be
alright. Everything will be alright.
You'll be alright. Come on.
I don't understand why Alaeddin Bey retreated.
All those Alps and martyrs.
Alaeddin!
Brother... Brother... Here.
Brother!
What do you think you are doing, huh? Why
did you retreat in the middle of the battle?
Why did you leave us alone
in the hands of infidels?!
What was I supposed to do?
If I hadn't retreated, all
the Alps would have died.
They should have!
We would all die there with our
honour there if necessary! But you...
But you should have let me
know before doing such a thing!
What do you think happened there?
Do you know what happened there? The infidels...
They all attacked us!
For our cause...
The Alps who fought for
our cause became martyrs!
We left our martyrs there!
Alaeddin. Look at my face!
Yusuf.
Yusuf and many other Alps...
They all became martyrs Alaeddin.
All of them!
Brother..
Look, you are saying wrong things...
-I did what was right.
-Shut up!
Shut up!
Tell me now!
How are we going to take our
martyrs from there, Alaeddin?
Tell me now, Alaeddin!
How are we going to look at
Osman Bey's face, Alaeddin?!
We could have gained a victory.
We lost because you retreated!
How can you be so arrogant, Orhan Bey?
You are blinded by your
ambition for victory! This is battle!
Retreating is as normal as attacking!
I retreated to protect
the lives of our valiants!
The right thing...
...was to retreat.
-Retreat? That was not retreating, brother.
That was running away, Cerkutay.
What will happen now?
Let me tell you what will happen
When we go back to the tribe...
You will answer for..
...all the things you did...
...before my father!
Enough! I had enough! Why do
you think you are right every time?!
I did what I thought
was right! I can go to my father...
...and explain everything gladly!
Don't worry!
Alaeddin!
You made the biggest
mistake in your life by retreating!
You fled from that battlefield in fear. You!
You..
You are a coward, Alaeddin!
At least, I am...
...a coward who worries about
the lives of our men! But you are...
...an unaware man who drags his men to death!
You are nothing else!
-My Shahzade!
-Stop! Look around you!
This is battlefield! There is shame in
cowardice and honour in moving forward!
But if you are saying you
want to use ink with scholars...
...in the madrasah(school)
then Alaeddin...
...then you...
...have nothing to do in the battlefield!
You shouldn't have done this, Orhan Bey!
You shouldn't have done this!
-Done what, huh?
-Who are you, huh?
Who are you to hit me?
-Who are you?
Let me, Cerkutay Bey!
How could you leave your brother there?
How could you betray your Alps and martyrs?
Who are you to hit me?
This is only the beginning! We will
celebrate many more victories together!
Never forget that the greatest
defeats come while celebrating victory.
Don't talk like that.
Commander Gladius!
Hristo
I went to meet the troops that
will come to Bursa as you ordered.
Good.
Where is my army, Hristo?
Osman.
He raided the place.
Get out.
Never underestimate him.
Look.
He destroyed half of your army.
You defeated his sons.
Not Osman himself.
When Osman stands before me..
I promise you, he won't be as lucky as his sons.
Dying in the battlefield will be a gift for him.
Gladius..
I have waited for years to
make him feel the greatest pain.
It's time.
Those looks in your beautiful eyes...
I even pity your enemy.
Tell me.
What is your plan?
I will...
...kill Osman with his own child's hands.
He will die writhing in the pain of his soul...
...before the pain in his body.
Osman Bey won a victory!
Thanks.
Thank you, thank you.
-May your victory be blessed, my Bey.
-Thank you.
-Are you alright?
-I am.
Orhan... Are you injured?
My Bey.
My sons... Are you alright?
What happened?
What happened at the outpost?
We were defeated, my Bey.
My Bey...
Villager Nicos who came to our tribe and
informed us about our Alps' situation...
...was the Byzantium Commander Gladius.
That dastard...
That dastard tricked us, my Bey.
And Alaeddin...
...left us there..
...and retreated.
-Patience, patience.
Because of Alaeddin..
...we returned to the tribe with defeat, my Bey.
Orhan Bey...
Do you think you are the only...
...commander of these valiants, huh?
-Alaeddin!
Bala.
If we hadn't retreated, we would
have been destroyed, my Bey.
But...
Orhan Bey's ambition
blinded him -When have we...
When have we run away from shahada, Alaeddin?
My Bey!
When did we run away from
shahada? We left Yusuf...
...our Alps, our martyrs behind us...
...and returned to our tribe with empty hands.
Now tell me Alaeddin Bey! Isn't what you did...
...isn't what you did shameful, huh?
My men burned alive there today!
The biggest shame for Beys is to
drag their men to death knowingly!
What are you saying?
-Are you going to teach me how to be a Bey?
Are you going to teach me how
to be a Bey? Know your limits!
Enough!
Your tongues became swords!
And you are hitting each other!
We don't even need enemies
when we have you two right now!
Yusuf...
My valiant...
He left a note, my Bey.
Your children are not...
...strong enough against me, Osman.
I am...
...waiting for you.
Gladius.
Do you see it now?
This is the end of the way you lead! See it!
Alaeddin!
Have some respect for the body here!
Get lost!
Don't you have a bit of shame, Alaeddin?
After all the things you did...
...will you come and sit at
the same table with my father?
Shame suits you...
...honour suits me.
I am always proud. -Is that so?
You left our martyrs in the
battlefield and ran away...
..and you will talk about honour
and pride before me here, huh?
Orhan Bey...
Watch your words.
Alaeddin... My father is
waiting for us, Alaeddin.
This situation makes me worried.
The conflict between Shahzades...
...overshadow our unity.
What will happen now, Beys?
My Osman Bey will calm them
down to bring peace, Aykurt.
God willing.
Let's not keep them waiting.
Come on Alaeddin.
Remove those two plates from the table.
My Bey.
I am telling you to take them away, Ulgen!
There is no place for those
two plates on this table!
No matter how many mistakes a child makes...
...there is always a place
for them at their father's table.
Don't, my Bey.
Don't, father.
I set this table for us to unite.
This place...
...is the most important
place for our family and state.
Those who shake it..
...those who bring destruction here...
...will not be let in this tent.
Daughters, you sit.
Those who have no place here know who they are.
What will happen now? How can we be separate?
We thought Halime would come
and that we would all be together...
Now this happened. We are losing each other.
-This matter will not be talked about today.
Ulgen. Come on, my daughter.
Put the meals on the plates.
Enjoy.
Do you like the result of your actions
Alaeddin? We were sent away...
...from my father's peaceful table.
-Enough.
We are in this situation
because of our ambition.
Even if you hit me once, even if you hit me for
a thousand times, the truth will not change.
And you are..
You are accusing me then.
Tell me Alaeddin.
Was I the one who left his brother...
...and martyrs in the battlefield?
Alaeddin..
...in that battlefield...
..because of your retreat..
...all our Alps were going to die.
Orhan Bey...
-Watch your words.
-I say this because I know the truth.
I am telling you the truth! And the truth
is, you ran away from that battlefield...
...because you were afraid, Alaeddin.
You should be thankful.
You should thank our father.
I am ignoring these words.
For now.
Are you happy with what you've done, brother?
Huh?
There is no unity in the tribe.
We could not take our martyrs.
How will we clean this dark stain, Cerkutay?
What was I supposed to do?
What? Would you not use your mind...
...and watch everyone become
martyrs while fighting for no reason?
No one would have come back to the tribe then.
At least, we would've died with our honour.
We would have been buried with honour.
We wouldn't be sitting here in embarrassment.
Brother..
If we died, we would be martyrs.
Now thanks to you...
...we are just a disgrace, Cerkutay.
Alaeddin Bey...
...is right. He did the
best thing by retreating.
Orhan Bey...
Orhan Bey was defeated by his
ambition. He shed brothers' blood.
And you..
Boran..
You should know what your
words can mean or else...
Or else?
Or else what, Cerkutay? What brother?
Or else, brother? What will happen?
Cerkutay Bey!
Boran Bey... Calm down.
Please, my Beys.
What are you doing? Does this suit you?
Don't, Beys.
Sow the wind, reap the whirlwind.
You are giving the infidels what they want.
If we look for separation...
...we will be destroyed and die out.
Koca Bey is right, brothers.
Let's kill infidels instead
of hurting each other.
Whenever the lineage of Oghuz
separated, they died. Union is strength.
Osman Bey is with you.
Do not let him down.
When the right time comes...
...he will tell you what is right.
Now is time to leave.
Go now.
Have a good night.
What is it about, Koca Bey?
It's not an important issue, my Bey.
Both sides are right in their own way.
Well..
They are fighting for the state in the end.
When the time comes,
their ambition will go away.
No.
There must be an issue.
Right, Koca Bey?
We need union...
...for the state.
If there is duality...
this will destroy the state
I know what to do to them.
Very beautiful.
She resembles your youth.
Right?
What are you doing here?
Do you remember? It's in the past but...
...when I was younger..
-Lower your voice.
I always wanted to come
to you before I left for battles.
I told you to lower your voice.
To see you for one last time. -Lower...
I don't want her to wake up.
And I don't want you to go to Osman.
There is no need for this.
Send a messenger.
Or something bad might
happen to you at the tribe.
I should do this to convince them.
Mongols are coming Gladius.
I have no other choice than talking to Osman.
Osman will trust you.
He will believe you.
He will trust me.
My Bey, you haven't slept all night.
This is the first time I
am seeing you like this.
Tell me... What are you thinking of doing?
-Whoever does harm to the...
...unity and strength of our state...
...even if they are my
children, I will never allow this.
No. I won't.
Boran!
Yes my Bey.
-Tell Orhan and Alaeddin to come here.
As you order my Bey.
My Alaeddin Ali..
Everyone knows why you did this.
You have prevented a great disaster
that was about to happen, Alaeddin.
I have.
I have, yes.
I left my martyr Alps behind, Gonca.
Now how are we going to look at their...
...mothers' and children's faces?
Alaeddin..
But with what you did...
...many Alps came back to their families.
I see my father like this
for the first time, Gonca.
I would enter the enemy's nest
alone rather than lose his trust.
I know. I know, of course.
Everyone knows this, Alaeddin.
You did not make a mistake.
It was Orhan Bey who was defeated...
...by his anger and who
hit you before all those Alps.
Can I come in, my Shahzade?
Come in, Aykurt.
-Peace be upon you. Peace be upon you too.
-My Shahzade.
Osman Bey wants to see you in his tent.
We lost our Alps and our men.
We were about to gain a
victory, but we lost because of him.
Because of the duality he
caused, for the first time in my life...
...I was sent away from...
...my father's love and table.
What can I say now? Huh?
When my own brother...
...did this to me..
...who am I going to trust, Holofira?
Can I come in, my Shahzade?
Come in Cerkutay.
My Shahzade.
Osman Bey is waiting for you.
-You called us, my Bey.
-Stop there!
You are not looking into the eyes...
...of your father.
This is the Bey of the state, Osman Bey.
Look what Orhan Bey caused
with what he did, Holofira.
You should know that...
...this fire will burn the tribe down.
When it is Alaeddin Bey who went against
his brother's orders and lost his trust...
..how can you accuse Orhan?
-Lost his trust?
Which trust are you talking about Hatun?
Can trust that is ruined at the
first difficulty be called trust?
Apparently, Orhan Bey is
ready to give up on his brother.
And this is his excuse.
You are the one who is looking for
an excuse and growing the fire, Gonca.
Orhan only cares about his cause.
Those who care about the cause
fight against infidels, Holofira.
They don't fight against their brothers.
Who are you trying to fool, huh?
But know this..
If Alaeddin gets hurt...
..I will hurt others even more.
Are you threatening me, Gonca?
I can burn the whole world for Orhan.
And I know this well that...
...even if you are trying to cause disorder...
...Orhan can make all infidels kneel
to protect Alaeddin from getting hurt.
He can.
Is that why he yelled at Alaeddin,
humiliated him before Alps...
...and told him to go back to mad rasa, huh?
Battlefield is different, Gonca!
I grew up in that field, Holofira!
I know the battlefield better than you!
But in the battlefield, we shed
enemies' blood, not brothers' blood!
What happened?
Didn't you know?
Did Orhan Bey not tell you that
he hit Alaeddin before all the Alps?
He did not.
I could not teach you anything as your father.
Nothing.
If someone...
...came to me and told me that..
...my children would fight...
..I would never believe this.
I would never believe this.
Never.
Shame on you..
Shame on you. Shame on you.. Shame on you..
Now...
You are both talking to the
ruler of the state, Osman Bey.
What is your problem? Tell me!
My Bey, we lost in a battle...
...when we were about to gain
a victory. That's why I am angry.
Orhan Bey is not telling
you all the details, my Bey.
We were caught unaware, and
we were in a difficult position.
No one could know if we
were going to win or lose.
We got into many battles until this day, my Bey.
With Allah's permission,
we survived in all of them.
Of course, we could not defeat our
enemies in all of them. But my Bey...
...when have we ever...
...left our men behind and run away?
I did not run away!
I retreated by following our morals. But you...
...you let your ambition...
-Shut up!
You are still nursing your grudge!
Look at me.
Listen to me carefully.
Whoever tries..
...to cause disorder and duality in my state...
I will never allow them.
Whoever tries to separate...
...my banner and my nation...
I will never allow them. Even
if they are my own children.
...I am Osman Bey.
I will never let this happen!
We need justice for the state!
We need unity for the state!
You should know.
In this struggle...
...whoever stands in my way...
...I will never allow them to move.
Therefore..
..you will either unite...
...or...
...I will...
...walk on this path without you.
Boran.
Yes my Bey.
Tell the Alps to get ready.
We will go and take our martyrs.
As you order my Bey.
No.
You will not come.
My sword is enough for me.
You snake!
Sofia.
What is happening?
You snake..
How could she come here?
What is she trying
to do this time?
She is approaching her death.
Sofia.
You demon! How could
you come to this tribe, huh?
Don't you know that I
won't let you survive here?
Bala!
Today, there will be no bloodshed. No death.
-There will be peace.
-Attention!
Osman Bey!
What is it?
Did you come to your own
death with your own feet?
No.
I am too young to die.
Today...
...I am here on behalf of Byzantium.
-For an alliance.
-Are we going to make an alliance with you?
We have a common enemy, Osman.
Olcaytu.
If Olcaytu takes your
lands, he will also take Bursa.
We are on the same side today.
The offer of the Mongol envoy.
Look.
Look carefully.
An alliance is your only option.
Olcaytu is coming.
Osman Bey.
This means destruction.
I would neither trust nor ally...
...with an executioner like you, who brought...
...unimaginable suffering to my family...
...and kidnapped my child.
Look! Taking your life is halal to me!
I can kill you here!
And then I can attack Olcaytu with all my power.
And I will also take Bursa for which...
...you offer peace to your enemy!
You still don't believe me, huh?
From now on, the only agreement we'll make is...
...to take your life without pain,
Sofia. Expect nothing else from us.
Alright.
I will convince you of my sincerity.
You stole my future from me Osman Bey.
In return for my unborn children...
...and the dreams...
..you took from me..
..I stole Halime from you.
We are even.
Now...
I will give you my most precious one
whom I raised with my own hands...
...Halime.
Sofia..
You are playing games again!
I told you, I am not playing
a game this time, Bala!
Giving her to you...
...is as painful as seeing Kayi flag in Bursa!
-Where is Halime?!
-Her name is not Halime! I named her Poena!
And she is in Bursa now.
And this time I am really telling you the truth.
Now..
...the decision is yours.
If you still..
...want your daughter back who hates Turks...
...I have only one condition.
Alliance against Mongols.